{
    "subject": "resource/How_Green_Was_My_Valley_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/John_Ford",
    "human_readable": "The director of the film 'How Green Was My Valley' is John Ford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886314272880554,
            "question": "Is John Ford the director of the movie 'How Green Was My Valley'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9662835597991943,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'How Green Was My Valley'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9531926512718201,
            "question": "Besides 'How Green Was My Valley', what other films has John Ford directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8892021775245667,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made 'How Green Was My Valley'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8549002408981323,
            "question": "What film is associated with John Ford as its director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8450062870979309,
            "question": "Name a film directed by John Ford."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5338024497032166,
            "question": "Who are some other notable directors from the same era as John Ford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5012785792350769,
            "question": "What genre is 'How Green Was My Valley'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4829154908657074,
            "question": "When was 'How Green Was My Valley' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4494425654411316,
            "question": "Which film won an Academy Award for Best Director under John Ford?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the film 'How Green Was My Valley' is John Ford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5590_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'How Green Was My Valley' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5590_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'How Green Was My Valley'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5590_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other notable directors from the same era as John Ford?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5590_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5590_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer to your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the director of the film 'How Green Was My Valley' is John Ford. This can be confirmed by looking at the context information where it says \"The movie \u201cHow Green Was My Valley\u201d was directed by John Ford.\" and also in other files where it mentions John Ford as the director of the film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"How Green Was My Valley\" was directed by John Ford, thus supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}